max.com 2019-03-30

# 

                                    PRIVACY POLICY
This privacy policy (this “Privacy Policy”) tells you about the information that Max
International, LLC (“Max,” “we,” “us” or “our”) collects in connection with the
operation of our website, www.max.com (the “Site”), how the information is used and
how you can access and correct certain information that we may collect.
Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information collected from you by
Max via the Site and does not apply to information obtained or disclosed through other
technology devices such as offline correspondence or personal contact with Max
representatives. Further, the Site may contain advertisements and/or links to other
entities’ websites that are not controlled or operated by Max. This Privacy Policy does
not apply to such third party websites, and Max is not responsible for the content of such
third party websites or the privacy practices of such third parties. Therefore, we
encourage you to request and review the privacy policies of any third parties upon
disclosing your information to such parties or visiting such third party websites.
This Privacy Policy is effective as of September 10, 2018 (the “Effective Date”).
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND REVISIONS TO THIS
PRIVACY POLICY
By using the Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy
Policy, you may not use the Site. Max reserves the right, in our discretion, to change,
modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time,
without prior notice to you. All revisions will be posted to the Site. We urge you to
review this Privacy Policy frequently for changes. Your continued use of the Site means
that you accept those changes.
INFORMATION COLLECTED AND HOW WE USE IT
We strive to allow you to always remain in control of the information you provide to
Max. In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing
personal information about yourself.
We do, however, collect information about visitors to the Site including: (i) personally
identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, email address, credit
card data, etc.), which you voluntarily submit to us as part of the Max Associate
enrollment process and/or when you purchase Max products directly from the Site, and
(ii) aggregate information (such as information about how many visitors log on to the
Site, the pages they access, etc.).
Max may use such personally identifiable information separately, in combination with
pre-existing information, or on an aggregate basis, for any legitimate business purpose
whatsoever in identifiable or de-identifiable form including:
                       To direct product shipments;
                       To communicate with you via email or telephone;

                       To send information about the Max Associate program and/or Max
                        products or services via email or telephone; or
                       To enforce our Terms of Use.
To better meet your needs, we may supplement the information we collect with data
obtained from third parties for the same purposes.
DATA SHARING AND TRANSFER
Max will not trade, sell or share your personal information for use by any third party
without your consent, unless required by law or as previously disclosed to you. Max
reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information based on the good
faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate to: (i) protect and defend the
rights or property of Max or (ii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the safety or
security of the public or of users of Max’s products or services and/or the Site.
Your personal information will generally be stored in the databases of a third party
service provider. These databases are typically located in the United States, but as
explained in the Cross Border Transfer section, may also be located outside of the United
States. Our policy is to ensure that your information is always granted the same level of
protection no matter where it is stored. In the event that Max is involved in a transaction
such as a merger, stock purchase or sale, or sale of substantially all of Max’s assets, your
personal information may be transferred to the other party in such transaction.
CROSS BORDER TRANSFER
Your personally identifiable information may be stored and processed in any country
where we have facilities and operations, and by providing any personally identifiable
information to us, you consent to the transfer of such personally identifiable information
to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may
have different data protection rules from your country of residence.
COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES
Cookies help us in many ways to make your visit to the Site more enjoyable and
meaningful to you. Cookies are text information files that your web browser places on
your computer when you visit a website. Max may use such “cookie” technology to
obtain non-personal information from you as an online visitor. Most browsers accept
cookies automatically, but can be configured not to accept them or to indicate when a
cookie is being sent. Max may also use analytical tools to monitor usage of the Site and
user activity on the Site.
CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
We take the utmost care to protect children’s privacy and take into consideration
appropriate national and international laws and regulations on children's privacy. The Site
does not knowingly collect information from and is not directed towards or intended to be
used by children under the age of thirteen (13) years old.
SECURITY

We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the personal information submitted to
us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of
transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is one hundred percent
(100%) secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to
protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
CHOICE AND OPT-OUT PREFERENCES
Other than cookies or other technological means, Max does not collect your personally
identifiable information unless you choose to provide it. If, at any time, you would like
to correct, update or delete your personally identifiable information, or if you prefer not
to receive any other form of communication from Max, please contact us via email at
support@max.com or via U.S. mail at:
Max International, LLC
102 South 200 East, Suite 610
Salt Lake City, UT 84111
SPECIAL NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year,
information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you or your
family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description
of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an
email to legal@max.com and please include the phrase “California Privacy Request” in
the subject line and provide us with your name, address and email address. We will
respond to you within thirty (30) days of receiving such a request.
BROWSER DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS
Although the Site currently does not have a mechanism to recognize the various web
browser Do Not Track signals, we do offer our customers choices to manage their
preferences. To learn more about browser tracking signals and Do Not Track please visit
http://www.allaboutdnt.org/
QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS
Max welcomes questions and comments about this Privacy Policy. Questions or
comments should be directed to Max’s General Counsel, who oversees Max’s
compliance with privacy requirements at:
Max International, LLC
102 South 200 East, Suite 610
Salt Lake City, UT 84111
legal@max.com
